<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>OniDevilstrand</defName>
	<label>Onistrand</label>
	<description>Fabric spun from combining devilstrand and oni feathers. A unique chemical reaction occur as they are spun together, further improving the protective properties of devilstrand. It is rumored to be as strong as the wool from the ancient Oni.</description>
	<baseCost>600</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
	<prerequisites>
		<li>Devilstrand</li>
	</prerequisites>
	<researchViewX>0</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>0.5</researchViewY>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>
	
<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>OniNewPlants</defName>
	<label>Sow Oni Plants</label>
	<description>Learn how to sow Oni cultivated variant plants: Featherleaf, Demon Breath and Yokai Peppers.\n\nNeed an Oni to research and figure out how to teach your colonists.</description>
	<baseCost>100</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Neolithic</techLevel>
	<researchViewX>0</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>2.5</researchViewY>
	<tags>
		<li>OniStart</li>
	</tags>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>
  
<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>YokaiPepperNarcotic</defName>
	<label>Yokai Narcotics</label>
	<description>Make yokai narcotic from extracting and blending yokai peppers and smokeleaf into a super concentrate, then mixing it with finely grinded medicinal herb paste. Also unlocks the blowpipe darts weapon.</description>
	<baseCost>400</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Neolithic</techLevel>
	<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>2.5</researchViewY>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>

<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>OniamineBasic</defName>
	<label>Oniamine production</label>
	<description>Refines Oni horn fragments and feathers into Oniamine, a unique precursor chemical that is used as the base for Oni drug synthesis. The production of an extremely addictive drug, Oni Dust, is also unlocked with this research.</description>
	<baseCost>400</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Neolithic</techLevel>
	<researchViewX>0</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>1.5</researchViewY>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>
  
<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>OniamineAdvanced</defName>
	<label>Oniamine extraction</label>
	<description>Extract Oniamine from Oni pelts, a unique precursor chemical that is used as the base for Oni drug synthesis. Can also extract Oniamine from Oni meat at the biofuel refineries if researched.</description>
	<baseCost>400</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Neolithic</techLevel>
	<prerequisites>
		<li>OniamineBasic</li>
	</prerequisites>
	<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>0.5</researchViewY>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>
  
<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>OniCombatDrug</defName>
	<label>Light Soma's</label>
	<description>Using Oniamine as the base, unique Oni drugs can be synthesized at a crafting spot or a drug lab. They provide strong boosts but lasts a short duration. This will allow production of Red Soma of the Body, Green Soma of the Health, and Blue Soma of the Mind. In the Event of addiction Soma is interchangable allowing any Light Soma to calm the addiction.</description>
	<baseCost>600</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
	<prerequisites>
		<li>OniamineBasic</li>
	</prerequisites>
	<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>1.5</researchViewY>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>
	
<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>OniBlackTalonDrug</defName>
	<label>Black Soma</label>
	<description>Allows an Oni the ability to manufacture a very powerful drug using the dangerously addictive Oni Dust as the base, with a need of a live Oni physical contact during the production. Has a more managable addiction than the unstable Oni Dust however unlike all other Soma this addiction is not interchangeable. Only Black Soma will calm the addiction. \n\nNeed an Oni to research this.</description>
	<baseCost>600</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
	<prerequisites>
		<li>OniCombatDrug</li>
	</prerequisites>
	<researchViewX>2</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>1.5</researchViewY>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>

<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>OniCultureFurniture</defName>
	<label>Oni culture furniture</label>
	<description>Build and craft Oni themed cultural furnitures and production facilities, such as their style of seating, beds and ground oven.\n\nOni-styled cushions are made at crafting spots or tailoring workbenches, that can serve as a sitting cushion.</description>
	<baseCost>100</baseCost>
	<techLevel>Neolithic</techLevel>
	<researchViewX>0</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>3.5</researchViewY>
	<tags>
		<li>OniStart</li>
	</tags>
	<tab>OniResearch</tab>
</ResearchProjectDef>

</Defs>