<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Oni of the Rim</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>Oni_of_the_Rim</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1632244750</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Oni_of_the_Rim_2_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>New mod settings available with the XML Extensions mod, made by Imranfish, which extends the functionality of XML patch operations, and allows for the easy creation of mod settings.

The new options include the settings to nerf or remove combat boosts from Oni combat drugs, disable wild Mega Owls from spawning, and disabling the Revenant Talon faction raids if that faction exists in your current game.

Bug fixes: Revenant Talons can now be toggled during world creation, and two weapon textures fixes for 1.2 and older version of the mod.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Oni_of_the_Rim</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>New update for the Oni of the Rim race mod, mostly to fixing some bugs, and most importantly to inform you of the body structure change to match with 1.3 with the addition of the tongue body part.
Oni Shogun bed should now be classed as Royal Beds for Royalty requirements. The Oni double beds will not share properties as the regular double beds requirements, because they are still essentially a inferior bed type than regular beds.
If you are in a on-going save, please inspect any Oni and Ancestral Oni you have as their health tab may be slightly messed due to how the base game tags hediffs to each body parts and adding or removing body parts from the codes may cause a mismatch to where prosthetic/bionics and missing body parts go.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>	

</Defs>